

Somerville MA USA ron@0xadada.pub linkedin.com/in/ron-a github.com/0xadada

Staff software engineer with a passion for building great products. Expertise and intuition in multiple technology stacks. Independently design and implement systems given loose business requirements and goals. Mentors other engineers.

Defined technical strategy and drove execution across Salsify, Cinch Financial, Nara Logics to implement products that are usable, accessible, delightful, performant, maintainable and cost effective. Built products that been seen by millions at Amazon, Walmart, Target and other big retailers with brands such as Levi's, 3M, and L'Oréal.

EXPERIENCE

- 2018-2023 Salsify ------ Boston MA Web application architecture and implementation, product dev, leadership.
- 2018- Unredacted Word ------- Cambridge MA Writer, translator, editing, publishing, retail sales (books), marketing.
- 2012-2016 Nara Logics ------ Cambridge MA Strategy, architecture and implementation, security, automation, mentor.
- 2004-2016 Visual Assault ------- Cambridge MA Founder, client services, implementation, UX, race car driving.
- 2011-2012 Boston Interactive ------ Boston MA Software implementation, client services, mentor.
- 2009-2011 Cambridge BioMarketing ------ Cambridge MA Software implementation, client services.
- 2007-2009 RDVO, Inc ------ Somerville MA Software implementation, open web standards evangelism.
- 2007-2007 n2N Commerce ------ Cambridge MA Software implementation, testing.
- 2003-2007 HP (Autonomy) ------ Cambridge MA Software implementation, testing, network administration.
- 2000-2002 Cyber Access, Rovia Inc, Dell (EMC) ----- Greater Boston MA Testing, network administration.

PUBLICATIONS

2021 The Society of the Spectacle by Guy Debord --- Unredacted Word, LLC Critical analysis, research, writing, translation, editing, typesetting.

EDUCATION

2015 MAS.S65 Blockchain Technologies ------ MIT Media Lab 2004 BS Computer Science & Cognitive Psychology ----- Northeastern University